[
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "In which Italian region is Bari located?",
    "correct_answer": "Apulia",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Marche", "Campania", "Calabria"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Geography",
    "question": "Which coast of Italy is Bari on?",
    "correct_answer": "Adriatic",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Amalfi Coast",
      "Riviera delle Palme",
      "Costa Smeralda"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "When was the Bari Cathedral constructed?",
    "correct_answer": "between the late 12th and late 13th centuries",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "late 11th century",
      "between the late 10th and late 11th centuries",
      "in the 12th century"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "History",
    "question": "Stylistically, this is an important example of which style?",
    "correct_answer": "Apulian Romanesque",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Gothic", "Baroque", "Modern"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Musicals_And_Theatres",
    "question": "In the 1980s, the theatre hosted two major operatic debuts which contributed to making the city world-famous, which ones?",
    "correct_answer": "'Iphigénie en Tauride' and 'I Puritani'",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "'Orfeo' and 'L’incoronazione di Poppea'",
      "'Giasone' and 'Venus and Adonis'",
      "'The Fairy-Queen' and 'L’Eraclea'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "Musicals_And_Theatres",
    "question": "The Petruzzelli, completely destroyed in the 1991, was reconstructed entirely and returned to the city on which year?",
    "correct_answer": "2009",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1998", "2020", "2000"]
  },
  {
    "category": "games",
    "question": "domanda1",
    "correct_answer": "risposta corretta",
    "incorrect_answers": ["errata", "errata", "errata"]
  },
  {
    "category": "games",
    "question": "domanda2",
    "correct_answer": "risposta corretta",
    "incorrect_answers": ["errata", "errata", "errata"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "What is the capacity of the San Nicola Stadium",
    "correct_answer": "58,270",
    "incorrect_answers": ["20,510", "30,870", "40,120"]
  },
  {
    "category": "Sports",
    "question": "Which animal represent the logo of Bari football team?",
    "correct_answer": "2009",
    "incorrect_answers": ["eagle", "horse", "cockerel"]
  }
]
